(Final Episode)
- Ji Hwan.
- Excuse me.
Yoon Jun Seo, what a surprise.
I didn't expect you to come.
Of course, I should come.
Where is Manager Kim?
Manager Kim?
Why do you think she would...
Ji Hwan, do you want something to drink?
She came.
Actually, she came yesterday as well.
Jun Seo, there you are.
Over there.
It's warm.
I heard you're going to study abroad.
Where did you hear that from?
I wanted to tell you myself.
I wanted to meet you before you leave.
So, I came here.
How are you holding up?
People say things are also hard
for the caregiver.
It's hard.
It's very tough.
I'm silly.
When you say it's hard,
I just want to help you out,
without a valid reason.
How have I become like this?
We should say our goodbyes here.
Let's forget everything that had happened.
I'll forget everything, and so will you.
Will you?
Bye.
Jun Seo.
I changed my mind.
I'll still forget everything,
but will you remember me?
Please think of me once in a while.
Remember how much I loved you
from all my heart.
If you don't, my love would be so pitiful.
Will you?
Of course...
I will.
I won't forget it.
All right.
Let me see.
It's fine.
I must've been hit somewhere.
Why did he go to Seoul,
leaving you alone like this?
He went to visit Ji Hwan's exhibition,
and he said he needed to meet someone.
It's important to him.
I told you not to disturb me.
Does it hurt a lot? Does it?
No.
No, only sometimes.
Do you want me to rub you?
Mommy's hand is a cure-all
My baby isn't sick anymore
Do you like it?
I love it.
It's the first time
you've done it to me, isn't it?
It is.
Mommy's hand is a cure-all
My baby isn't sick anymore
Nothing much has changed
I will see you next week.
Thank you.
How...
How can I notice if I get worse?
How can I know if I'm getting worse?
How can I know?
There are various signs and symptoms.
Have you had hemoptysis yet?
Hemoptysis?
Do you mean "cough up blood?"
Could you take pictures of me?
Take pictures?
Yes.
Let's take pictures.
I want to take pictures
while I still look fine.
Will you?
Will you take pictures?
No.
Because other people can see
your pictures, too.
I want to remember this later.
When I get better,
I would say I used to be sick like this.
I'll remember that.
Can you take pictures?
You are so bad at making porridge.
It's surprisingly bland and tasteless.
You can't have anything salty,
so just eat up.
Does yours taste better?
Of course.
Why are you eating this?
Why are you eating the same thing as mine?
How about I cook something good for you?
No. That's fine.
I don't want to eat anything else.
Let's just eat this.
It's not tasty at all.
Tae Seok.
Have you eaten well?
Have you seen the doctor regularly?
Did you miss me?
You always smile when I want your answer.
I've missed you.
You should've come more often to see me.
I'm a very busy man.
Why should I come here, anyway?
To check if you're happy with Jun Seo?
No.
Do you like roses?
Thanks.
That's so beautiful.
You're more beautiful.
No way, I look worse and worse.
Yes, you had better do that.
Then you will look ugly even to my eyes.
What should I do
if even you come to dislike me?
What's the matter? You have Jun Seo.
He seems not to like me these days.
Look at him.
I see.
Jun Seo, it's been a while.
Right. There you are.
I was coughing on the bus the other day,
and a boy in front of me looked at me.
Then he mimicked me coughing.
Did he?
I kept coughing, but it was so funny.
Isn't that funny?
Yes, it is.
Tae Seok.
Why don't we take pictures
since you're here?
Take pictures?
I have taken a lot of pictures.
Have you?
Can you bring me a camera?
Let's take pictures.
I want to take pictures with Tae Seok.
All right.
Okay.
I'll bring it, then.
You didn't even laugh
when I told you a funny story.
I'll bring it.
- No.
- I'll bring it.
Do you think that was funny?
Was it funny you were coughing
because you're sick?
Do you think it's fun to talk
as if you're dying?
Jun Seo.
Do you think I'm funny, too?
Is it also funny...
to see how I'm concerned about
whether you're sick or in pain?
Eun Seo, this morning, did you...
I'm sorry, Tae Seok.
He really hates me, doesn't he?
You're right.
Save her.
Please save her.
Save her, please.
Save Eun Seo, please.
They love each other so much,
so I let her be with him.
Please don't take her away.
Please save her.
Right.
It came out well.
I'm very sick, aren't I?
I got much worse, didn't I?
Why don't we have dinner...
with Mom, Dad, and everyone some time?
Please keep these photos with you.
Whether I'm pretty or not,
I believe you'll keep them.
You should keep them...
since I might be gone soon.
Eun Seo.
I'm just saying...
I might be gone.
I don't mean I will be gone.
Don't hate me.
I feel so bad for you because I'm sick.
But what can I do if you hate me?
When you like me,
there is nothing I want anymore. Right?
I like you.
All I have is you.
My life is...
all about you from the beginning
to the end,
I'm like this because I love you so much.
So, I won't let you go.
Don't worry.
I won't let you go alone.
Soon Im,
why are you drinking in broad daylight?
You.
It's none of your business if I drink.
Why do you care?
My unfortunate fate ruined
even my daughter's life.
Why do you care?
What are you doing here?
Give me a drink, too.
Did you go to Eun Seo?
I don't think you did.
How dare I go there?
I think Professor Yoon was coming, too.
I thought so. That's why I'm here.
I thought you would probably be sad.
I don't need anything.
I need nothing at all.
I don't need anything at all.
Mom, you have to be strong.
Don't lose hope, please.
Mom.
Cheers to our dinner.
Cheers.
I'm doing well enough, aren't I?
Yes?
You did a good job.
You were so beautiful that day.
Can I brush your hair?
Goodness, please don't take her away
before me.
You can't take her before me.
Okay.
Okay, I'll beat this, mom.
Mom, don't cry.
Mom, these are...
Jun Seo gave them to me.
He asked me to keep them.
He said he couldn't keep them.
Go inside.
I'll be with you soon after cleaning up.
All right.
Eun Seo.
I can't tear them.
It's not easy, Jun Seo. I can't tear them.
Eun Seo, what are you doing?
You wanted to take these pictures.
I wanted them,
and it's my choice to tear them.
I can tear them if I want to.
Eun Seo.
Don't yell at me. You can't yell at me.
What's the matter with you, Eun Seo?
Are you going to die?
Are you really going to die?
If I die, would you follow me?
Are you going to die?
Are you?
Why are you...
Why are you going to die following me?
Why?
Promise me.
Promise me that
you won't think about dying, ever.
Promise me now.
Promise me.
No.
I can't.
You're asking me to live without you.
Promise me.
No.
Eun Seo.
How can I live without you?
How can you be so cruel?
How can I live?
I can't live.
I don't want to live with that pain.
Can you do that if you were me?
But, please live.
Please live for me.
I'm dying now.
And you also want to be dying,
so should we spend my final moments
dying in unison?
Why are you making me do
such a horrible thing?
You said you love me.
Would you like to make me kill you?
Promise me.
I promise you.
I will take a vow.
I, Yoon Jun Seo,
will love and cherish Choi Eun Seo
all the days of my life.
Will you, Choi Eun Seo,
love and cherish Yoon Jun Seo
all the days of your life?
I will.
I absolve you from your sins.
Jun Seo.
Eun Seo.
Can you take me to the beach?
When I look back, we were always together.
We were.
Do you have anything you regret, Eun Seo?
No, I don't regret anything.
Because I have you.
All the people who I leave behind.
Dad, Mom,
and Tae Seok.
I don't worry about them.
Because you will take care of them.
Will you?
I will.
I'll take care of them.
So, you have nothing to worry about.
Throughout my life,
without missing a moment,
I have loved you...
every moment of my life.
You know that, don't you?
I know.
Because I have loved you, too.
Thank you.
I...
want to take a nap.
Can you give me a piggyback ride?
Tell me something, Jun Seo.
I want to fall asleep listening to you.
What are we...
going to do tomorrow?
What?
Well, tomorrow...
I'll think of you as soon as I wake up.
I will think of you...
and sort out your photos.
Are you asleep, Eun Seo?
Yes.
And...
I'll call Mom and Dad
to tell them how you are.
Then we'll have lunch.
And...
Eun Seo.
I love you.
I love you so much.
Do you know that, Eun Seo?
Eun Seo, you know that, don't you?
What should we do tomorrow
in the afternoon?
Should we just take a nap
Eun Seo.
No.
Let's go for a walk.
We'll take a walk...
along the path you like.
Then in the evening,
we will make a fire...
and drink beer.
What do you think?
Eun Seo.
Jun Seo.
Thank you for coming.
Tae Seok is here, too.
I'll get him.
Go in.
Go in and say goodbye to Eun Seo.
What is this, Choi Eun Seo?
You didn't keep any promises.
What are you doing?
What have you done?
You couldn't have saved Eun Seo.
What were you doing?
What did you do?
I can't remember Eun Seo's face
since yesterday.
I might have forgotten it.
I can't remember it at all.
How can I live now?
How can I live?
I have nothing left.
What can I hold onto now to live?
I can't even remember her face.
What should I do?
Jun Seo.
How can you live?
How?
I'll keep my promises to Eun Seo.
I will.
Good for you.
That's good for you.
You have promises to keep, at least.
Is that a good thing?
You have no idea...
how harsh that is.
Tae Seok, I have a favor to ask you.
What is it?
Take care of her funeral until the end.
I want to say "farewell" to her
in my own way.
So, you take care of that.
Can you do that?
Eun Seo would like that, too.
Before I keep my promises to you,
I want to be here one more time.
The happiest time,
the most beautiful time.
And this place.
I want to say goodbye to you here.
Then...
I'll live right here where you left...
wondering how long I'll live,
and looking forward to
when you will call for me.
Jun Seo.
Eun Seo.
(Thank you for watching
"Autumn in My Heart.")